Guide to the Native American Educational Services, Robert Rietz Papers 1876-1982
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Publications
  - Subseries 1: Indian Reservations, Official Newsletters and Bulletins
    - Rosebud Reporter, Rosebud Agency, Rosebud, South Dakota (1953-54) and Rosebud Sioux Herald (Eyapaha), Rosebud, South Dakota (1970), Folder 5: The Ute Bulletin, Uintah and Ouray Agency, Fort Duchesne, Utah (1951) Folder 6: Colorado River Agency Newsletter, Parker, Arizona (1952-1954) Folder 7: Smoke Signals. Colorado River Indian Tribes, Parker, Arizona (1970) Folder 8: Papago Indian News, Papago Indians, Sells, Arizona (1954) Folder 9: Fort Apache Scout Official Newspaper, White Mountain Apache Tribe, Fort Apache Indian Reservation, Whiteriver, Arizona (1970) Folder 10: Klamath Reservation News, Klamath Agency, Oregon (1953) Folder 11: Consolidated News, Fort Belknap and Rocky Boy’s Reservations, Harlem, Montana (1953-54) Folder 12: Northern Cheyenne Agency, Lame Deer, Montana (1953) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Winnebago Reservation News (1951-54) and Ho Chunk Wazee ja chee rla, Wisconsin Winnebago Business Committee for its Tribe (1962), Folder 14: Redlake Neighborhood Centers Newsletter, Red Lake Reservation, Minnesota (1970) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Si Wong Ghe. The Cattaraugus Indian Reservation Newspaper, Seneca Nation Community Action Agency, New York (1970)., Folder 16: Longhouse News, Caughnawaga Indians, Canada (1970) (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 2: Scientific Publications. Journals and Articles
    - Journals. Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences, 1948., Folder 2: Journals. The American Indian, 1950-1952. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Journals. The American Indian, 1955-1959. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Journals. Plains Anthropologist. Journal of the Plains Conference, 1961. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Journals. Ethnohistory, 1963., Folder 6: Journals. Current Anthropology. 1971. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Articles by Author. AAVV - Aberle (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Articles by Author. Barnouw - Enochs (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Articles by Author. Gifford – Gillin (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Articles by Author. Graymont – Harper (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Articles by Author. Kluckhohn – Lowie (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Articles by Author. Malan - Malouf (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Articles by Author. McKern – Provinse (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Articles by Author. Redfield – Roberts (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Articles by Author. Skinner (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Articles by Author. Smith (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Articles by Author. Spoehr (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Articles by Author. Steward – Tiedke (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Articles by Author. Vogt – Wahrhaftig (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3: Conference Proceedings, Unpublished Papers and Reports
    - Indians of the United States. Second Inter-American Conference on Indian Life, Peru. 1948. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Institute on American Indian Assimilation. 1952. Sponsored by Association on American Indian Affairs and The American Indian Fund. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Conference on Indian Affairs, South Dakota. 1955 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - First Annual Conference for Tribal Judges, South Dakota.1959 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - The Navaho Urban Relocation Research Project. Symposium presented at the American Anthropological Association, 1965. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Wisconsin Indian Leadership Conference. 1963, 1967. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Annual Conference, Native American Church of North America. 1968. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - National Congress of American Indians. Proceedings, Resolutions, Addresses. 1953-1962. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Reports on the Utes, Ojibwa, Navaho, Teton-Dakotas, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Report on Wisconsin Winnebago Project, Report on Cherokee, Mission Indians, Army Engineers, Sourcebook on the Navajo, 1960-1968. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Papers by Author. Davids – Downs et al. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Papers by Author. Gearing – Hlady (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Papers by Author. Lee – Rietz (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Papers by Author. Sady – Tax (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Papers by Author. Thomas – Warne. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Papers by Author. Wahrhaftig – No Author. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 4: Newspaper Clippings
    - Newspaper Clippings. 1931-1950. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings. 1951. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings. 1952. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings. 1953. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings. 1954. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings. 1955-1970. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 5: Federal and State Government Publications
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Division of Indian Health. Indians on Federal Reservations. 1958-1960. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Division of Indian Health. Indians on Federal Reservations. 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Division of Indian Health. Indian Health and US Indian Population and Land. 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - US Senate. Committee on Appropriations (Federal Facilities for Indians). Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs (Omaha Tribe). 1961-1962. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Interior. Bureau of Indian Affairs. “Indians.” 1963 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Department of the Interior. News Releases. 1961-1966. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Department of the Interior. Bureau of Indian Affairs. Brochures, Manual Indian School Service, Industrial Development Program. 1941-1964. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Interior. Survey Report on the Bureau of Indian Affairs, Report of the Commissioner to the Secretary of the Interior. 1952-1954. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Interior. Indian Land Tenure, Economic Status, and Population Trends. 1935. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Publications of the Bureau of Indian Affairs, Federal Indian Schools. 1947 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - US Indian Service, Office of Education, Bureau of Indian Affairs, Branch of Higher Education. Scholarships and Indian Graduates. 1968-1972. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - California Senate Committee on Indian Affairs, Brochure on Termination. 1955-1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Wisconsin Indians, North Dakota History, Indian in Arizona, New Mexico Commission on Indian Affairs. 1952-1962. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - South Dakota Department of Public Instruction, State University Bulletin, Flandreau High School Seniors. 1947-1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - South Dakota Newsletter, Employment Security Department. Aberdeen News, Areal Employees’ Association. 1954. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - North Dakota Chapter of IAPES News (International Association of Personnel in Employment Security). 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - North Dakota, Chamber of Commerce Newsletter (Fargo and Minot). 1954. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - North Dakota State Employment Service, Farm Labor Bulletin. 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - North Dakota. State Welfare and Employment Statistics, Land Use Planning, Census, Indian Land (1940-1952) (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - North Dakota. State Employment Service, Business Survey (1953-1954) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 6: Non-Governmental American Indian Publications
    - American Indian Art. Exhibition Brochures, Denver Art Museum, Iroquois and Native American Art of Today. 1945-1951. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Indian Rights Association: Indian Truth, Forth Hall Story, The Five Civilized Tribes of Oklahoma. 1951-1961. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - National Congress of American Indians: News Bulletin, Constitution, Sentinel Bulletin. 1951-1970. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - American Indian Center (Chicago): A Little Newspaper About Indians, Tom Tom Echoes Echoes. 1953-1954. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Association on American Indian Affairs: News Letter. 1954-1981. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - National Indian Youth Council. ABC. 1964-1965. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - American Indian Directory: Indian Lore, Chicago. Undated-1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - American Indian Center (Cleveland): The Cleveland Crier. 1970. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - American Friends Service Committee: Program Summary. Pamphlet, Indians of California. Undated - 1969. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Indians Illustrated, Wassaja The Indian Historian, Cherokee Indian Fair. 1968-1980. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Indian League of the Americas Newsletter. American Indian United: Indian Uprising. United Scholarship Service News. 1969-1970. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - A Program for Indian Citizens. Commission on the Rights, Liberties, and Responsibilities of the American Indian. The Fund for the Republic 1961. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Harvard Law Record, Friends Committee on National Legislation, The First American. 1954-1965. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Local Publications. Indian Times (Colorado), Indian Programs (Arizona), The Amerindian (Chicago), The Red Man’s Crisis (Oklahoma). 1953-1970. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Religious Publications. Indian Affairs Bulletin (Congregational Christian Churches, United Church of Christ), Indian Youth Magazine. 1958-1968. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Religious Publications. National Council of Churches, National Fellowship of Indian Workers. The Christian Century. 1960-1966. (Box 28, Folder 16)